Part 3
Speaker: Walid walks for five days through the mountains.
The sun shines, and at night it’s very cold.
Then, one evening, he finds the palace.
The prince welcomes him and gives him food and drink, and a comfortable bed.
But Walid can’t sleep. He’s thinking about the one thousand gold coins.
The next morning, he says to the prince,
‘I want to say thank you to you. Please have this silver ring. It’s my mother’s.’
The prince is very happy. ‘This is a beautiful ring,’ he says.
‘Thank you. Let me give you something in return.’
He gives Walid a box.
‘Don’t open this until you get home,’ he says.
‘Be careful with it. It’s very, very valuable.’
Walid runs through the mountains, and after three days he arrives home.
‘Where’s my silver ring?’ shouts his mother.
‘Don’t worry about your ring!’ says Walid.
‘Look at this!’
Hassan and their mother watch as he opens the box.
Inside he finds the glass bottle.